想不想听点爆炸新闻
Wanna hear something crazy?
有什么爆炸新闻
What's that?
从洛杉矶登机的时候  你看见那个大块头了吗
Did you see the big guy when we got on in L.A.?
坐头等舱  卷发  带吉他的那个
Sitting in first class, curly hair, guitar case?
他怎么了
What about him?
他是大洋航空六人之一
He's one of the Oceanic Six.
真是个意志坚强的家伙
Guy's got nerves of steel, man.
整架客机坠毁了  他幸存了
He survives a full-on commercial airliner crash.
现在又回来  还是坐去南太平洋的飞机
Now he's back flying over the same south Pacific?
是啊  也许他觉得
Yeah, well... maybe he doesn't believe
闪电不可能两次都劈一个地方吧
that lightning will strike twice in the same place.
你还好吗  Frank
You all right there, Frank?
一切正常
I'm just fine.
系紧安全带
Fasten seat belt
老兄
Dude...
你可能需要系紧安全带
You might wanna fasten your seat belt.
不是吧
Oh,no.
怎么了
What?
关闭自动驾驶  我来操纵
Autopilot off! I got the controls.
自动驾驶已关闭  你来操纵
Autopilot off. You have the controls.
拉起来
Pull that rudder!
怎么回事
What?
怎么会这样
What?!
-失速  失速  -我们没有燃料了
- Stall. Stall. - We've lost power!
-失速  -重启  1
- Stall. - Restarting one.
重启  2
Restarting two.
高度650
Altimeter reads 650.
哦  我的天啊
Oh, my god.
再给我点动力  我能把咱们都拉起来
Give me more power! I can pull us out of this!
-你会害我们摔得粉身碎骨  -照我说的办
- You're gonna rip us apart! - Do it!
拜托  拜托
Come on. Come on.
那边能当跑道吗
Is that a runway?
多处机械失灵  咱们得降落
Massive instrument failure! We're puttin' her down!
呼救  呼救  呼救  Ajira航空3-1-6呼救
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! This is Ajira 3-1-6!
呼救  呼救  呼救
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
-15  16  -全襟翼
- 50... 60... - Full flaps!
减速  飞行速度190
Gear down! Airspeed 190!
降落角度太大
We're coming in too steep!
反向助推
Reverse thrusters!
来啊
Come on!
跑道不够了  我们要跑出去了
We're runnin' out! We're runnin' out!
停下
Hold on!
注意  要撞上了
Brace for impact!
喂  女士
Hey,lady.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你是Jarrah吗
Jarrah?
不是  我叫Caesar  咱们遇到事故了
No. My name is Caesar. We had an accident.
但是咱们还活着
But we're okay now.
Frank
Frank?
Sun
Sun.
你没事吧
You all right?
天啊  发生什么了
Oh,my god. What happened?!
我也不知道
I don't know.
大家都去哪儿了
Where's everyone else?
Jack  还有
Jack and...
Kate还有Hurley  他们去哪儿了
Kate and Hurley... where'd they go?
他们不见了
They're gone.
不见了
Gone?
去哪儿了
Gone where?
我怎么知道
How would I know?
30年前
Thirty Years Earlier
你还活着
You're alive.
哥们儿
Dude!
我都不敢相信
I can't believe it!
一下就把我抱起来了  金刚
Easy on the ribs there, Kong.
金刚
"Kong."
我真怀念这个外号
I actually missed that.
我也想你  Hugo
I missed you,too, Hugo.
Sawyer
Sawyer.
大夫
Doc.
见到你真高兴  Kate
Good to see you, Kate.
见到你也很高兴  James
You,too,James.
你们还真来了
You're really here.
那混蛋真做到了
Son of a bitch actually did it!
Locke说他要把你们带回来  可是
Locke said he was gonna bring you back,but...
他自己呢
Where is he?
John死了
John's dead.
死了?
Dead?
怎么回事
How?
那不重要  总之他已经去了
Doesn't matter. He's gone.
你们为什么要穿达摩的制服呢
So what's up with you guys and the old Dharma jumpsuits?
你没跟他们说吗
You didn't tell 'em?
没  我想让你跟他们说
No. I was waiting for you.
跟我们说什么
Tell us what?
我们加入了达摩组织
We're in the Dharma initiative.
他们回岛上了吗
They came back to the island?
不是  是我们回到过去了
No. We came back.
你们也是
And so did you.
现在是1977年
It's 1977.
你说  什么
What?
你是不是说
So you're telling me
你们这三年,一直在这跟达摩组织一起住
That you've been here,living with the Dharma initiative For the past three years?
没错
That's right.
你们登上直升机之后  到现在是多久
How long's it been for you since the chopper?
3年了
Three years.
Jin  我是Miles  请报告方位  完毕
Jin,this is Miles. Where are you? Over.
我要是不尽快回复  他们会派人来找
If I don't report in soon, they'll send out a patrol.
咱俩怎么处理他们
What should we do with them?
哥们儿  你英语说太牛了
Dude, your English is awesome.
我们要做的  就是把他们也带进来
What we do is we bring 'em in.
-把我们带哪儿去  -带回达摩村
- Bring us in where? - Back to the barracks at Dharmaville.
丛林里很多敌人
You can't be wandering around
你们不能在林子里瞎转
In the jungle with the hostiles.
什么敌人
"The hostiles"?
-"其他人"  -飞机上其他人怎么办
- The others. - What about everyone else from the plane?
他们可能还在那里
They could still be out there.
你什么意思  什么其他人
What do you mean, everyone else?
不光我们几个回来了
We didn't come back alone.
飞机上还有Sayid  还有Lapidus
Sayid was on the plane,too. Lapidus...
还有Sun
And Sun.
Jin  等等
Jin! Hold up!
- 你要去哪儿  - 去火焰站
- Where you goin'?! - The Flame.
如果有飞机降落在岛上  Radzinsky肯定会发现
If a plane landed on the island, Radzinsky will know.
等等  我们得考虑清楚
Hold on! We gotta think about this!
好吧  随他去
All right. That's it.
听我的  你们几个一定要待在一起
Listen, you guys gotta stay put.
哪儿也不要去  什么也不要做  一直到我想清楚
Don't go nowhere, don't do nothing till I can figure out
怎么解释你们从哪儿来
How the hell to explain where you came from.
Sawyer  等等
Sawyer,wait.
除了你和Jin  还有谁在这里
Other than you and Jin, who else is still here?
Miles  你看到James了吗
Miles,have you seen James?
没看到
Nope.
他也不应答对讲机
He's not answering his walkie,either.
Jin今早给他打过电话
Jin called him this morning,
然后他二话不说就跑出去了
Then he just ran off without telling me what was going on.
好吧  咱们看看能查到什么
Well, let's see what we've got.
看这个
Hang on.
他在那
There he is.
你看没看见我那件大号运动衫
You seen my baggy sweatshirt,
印着斗牛犬的那件
The one with the bulldog on it?
在洗衣房里
It's in the laundry.
James  出什么事了
James... what's going on?
他们回来了
They're back.
不好意思没听懂  谁回来了
I'm sorry. Who's back?
Jack  Hurley  Kate
Jack, Hurley, Kate.
什么
What?
是啊
I know.
他们回来了  Juliet
They came back, Juliet.
他们现在在这里吗
Are they here now?
他们现在在东边
They're out at the north point,
等着我去告诉他们接下来怎么办
Waitin' for me to tell 'em what to do.
他们是怎么回来的
How did they get...
我也不知道  他们说是坐飞机回来的
I'm not sure. They said they were on a plane.
我也不比你明白多少
I don't understand it any more than you do.
但是他们确实就在这里
But they're here,
趁还没人发现他们
And I gotta find a way to bring 'em in
趁他们还没毁掉咱们在这里的成果
Before somebody else finds 'em
我得找个方法把他们带回来
and they screw up everything we got here.
今天下午  有个潜艇要来
There's,um,a sub coming in this afternoon.
你学没学过敲门
You understand the concept of knocking?
把你脏手拿开
Get your hands off that!
我记得你听得懂英语 我说把手拿开
I thought you learned English. I said,hands off!
除了我  任何人都不许碰这个站的任何装置
Nobody handles any of the gear in this station except me.
明不明白
Understand?
我得查查雷达日志
I need to check the radar logs.
查它干嘛
For what?
求你了 我得弄清楚有没有飞机降落在岛上
Please. I need to know if a plane landed on the island.
有没有飞机降落?落到这儿?
If a plane landed? Here?
是
Yes.
什么意思  你觉得要是有飞机降落到咱们岛上
What,so you think if a plane landed on our island,
我还能像没事儿一样搭模型吗
I'd be over there just building my model?
我还能谁都不通知吗
That I wouldn't have called anyone?
我还能不拉警报吗
That I wouldn't have put out an alert?
也可能你没看到
Maybe you missed it.
能不能跟别的站确认一下
Can you check with the other stations?
我刚才跟你说了  我不可能
I just told you I would not be...
跟别的站问问
Check with the other stations.
所有站点请注意
Attention all stations,
火焰站Radzinsky
This is a system-wide broadcast
向全网广播
From Radzinsky at the Flame.
我想查找
I'm checking in
是否有人看到有飞机降落本岛
To see if anyone's seen an airplane over the island.
目前没人发现飞机
No one else has seen an airplane,
但是你要真看到了  请联系我  完毕
But if you have,could you call in to me,please? Over.
你这么着急到底是因为什么  Kwon
So what are you all hot and bothered about,Kwon?
这架飞机怎么就这么重要吗
Why is this plane so damn important?
反正就重要
It just is.
你在找人吗
Did you lose someone?
什么意思
Excuse me?
我看你四处张望
I just saw you looking around.
我想  你可能在找飞机上的人
I thought maybe you lost someone on the plane.
没有
No.
我自己上的飞机
I was traveling alone.
大家能不能听我说两句
Can I get everybody's attention?!
大伙请听我说
Everybody,please!
大家好好听
Listen up,folks!
我们现在处境是
Here's where we're at.
无线电失灵
The radio's dead,
所以我至今无法报告咱们的情况
So I haven't been able to call in our situation.
但是没关系
But that's all right.
他们一旦发现
Soon as they figure out
我们不在预定地点
We're not where we're supposed to be,
他们会展开搜索
They'll come looking for us.
所以现在最佳做法  就是聚集在一起
So best thing to do right now is just stick together.
待在一块儿  不要乱走
Stick together, hunker down
-等待救援到来  - 这是哪里
- And just wait till help gets here. - And where is here?
-什么  -这是哪里  这是什么地方
- What's that? - Where is here? What is this place?
我也不知道这是什么地方
I don't know where "here" is
因为我航空图上没有这个岛
Because this island's not on my charts.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
那边有几处房屋
Because there are some buildings over there...
还有牲畜的笼子
And animal cages
就能看见对面有个更大的岛
You can see a bigger island across the water.
那你就去那边找张新航空图吧
So maybe you should get some new charts.
眼下
Right now,
我要做的就是保证大家安全
I'm just trying to keep everyone here safe.
所以大家先收集些柴火吧
So let's gather up some firewood.
他想等  就让他自己等吧
If he wants to wait,let him!
我提议大家去查看一下那些房子
I say we search these buildings!
说不定他们有无线电  还有吃的
Maybe they have a radio or some food!
谁愿意来帮我
Who wants to help me?!
为什么跟踪我
Why are you following me?
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
回我们自己的岛
Back to our island.
你也想来吗
You wanna come?
Juliet
Juliet?
嗨  Amy
Hey, Amy.
-不好意思  我不是故意吵醒你的  - 不  没关系
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to wake you. - Oh,no,it's fine.
我来拿潜水艇人员名单
I just came to get the sub manifest.
-显然  我今天不想让你操劳  -谢谢你
- Obviously, I don't want you working today. - Thank you.
-满员了?  -差不多
- Full load? - Almost.
有两名队员在最后时刻退出了
Two of the recruits dropped out in the eleventh hour.
他们不愿在旅途中注射镇静剂
They didn't want to take the sedative for the trip.
能帮我看看Pierre吗
Can you tell Pierre for me?
你好  小家伙
Hello,little one.
你和Horace想好名字了吗
Have you and Horace decided on a name?
想好了  我们给他起名Ethan
Yeah,we have. We're gonna name him Ethan.
你好  小朋友
Oh,hey,buddy.
你和Jim什么时候也要个孩子
So... when are you and Jim gonna have one of these?
我不知道
I don't know.
等到时机成熟
Timing's gotta be right.
告诉你怎么回来的那个女的
So the woman who told you how to come back...
告没告诉你会回到30年前
Did she mention that it would be 30 years ago?
没  没说  她没提这个
No. No, she left that part out.
那我们现在该怎么办
So what are we supposed to do now?
我也不知道
I'm not sure yet.
Sawyer回来了
Sawyer's back!
好了  听着  你们要装成
All right,listen. Y'all are gonna be
坐潜艇来的第二批队员
The second batch of recruits comin' in off the sub
潜艇马上就进港了  我们时间很紧
Pullin' into port right about now, so we ain't got much time.
西装不错啊  大夫  可惜不适合岛上穿  试试这个
Nice suit,doc. Not exactly island wear. Try this.
你让我们说自己是坐潜艇来的
You want us to say we came in on the sub.
管用吗
How's that gonna work?
他们来的时候都被麻醉了
Everyone gets knocked out before the trip,
所以我们下手之前  他们根本不认识对方
So no one meets each other until we process 'em.
听着  我们得找到飞机上其他人
Look,we need to find the rest of the people from the plane.
如果飞机在这  Jin会找到的
If there was a plane, Jin will find it.
我们大概有10分钟时间对口供
So we got about ten minutes to make intake,
不然你们就要在丛林里长期扎营
Or y'all are gonna be camping in the jungle for a long time.
6个月之内不会有下一批雇员来
There ain't another batch of recruits due in for six months.
你们觉得如何
What do you think?
我觉得我们应该听Sawyer的
I think we should listen to Sawyer.
-我投票给不野营  -相信我
- I vote for not camping. - Trust me.
照我说的做  一切都没问题
Do what I say. Everything will be fine.
咱们走吧
Let's move.
刚接到潜望镜站电话
I just heard from the Looking Glass.
他们是最后一个打进来的站点
They were the last station to check in.
除了即将进站的潜艇  什么都没有
They got nothing but an incoming sub.
要不你先回家 有事我给你打电话
Why don't you go home, And I'll call you if something happens?
走开  走开  别挡我路
Move. Move. Out of my way.
-那群混蛋  -你看到什么了
- Those bastards. - What do you see?
坐标325  动力传感警报被触发
Grid 325. Motion sensor alarm was tripped.
我们附近有敌人
We got a hostile inside the perimeter.
你要去哪儿
Where you going?!
站住别动
Stop right there!
Sayid
Sayid?
Jin
Jin?
Sun在哪儿
Where's Sun?
我也不知道
I don't know.
闭嘴
Shut up!
蹲下
Get down!
再敢说一个字  老子毙了你
Say another word, and you're dead.
好吧  现在是1977年
Okay, so it's 1977.
对
Yep.
而且  你们都是达摩的人
And... you guys are all members of the Dharma initiative.
对
Yep.
那你也知道这些人后来都被屠杀了  对吧
Well,you do realize those dudes get wiped out,right?
我是说  你见过那个万人坑
I mean,I saw the pit where all the bodies got dumped.
-什么  -你不想吗
-what about it? -well,aren't you gonna warn 'em?
你不想在事情发生前去制止它吗
aren't you gonna stop it from happening?
我不是来给他们算命的
i ain't here to play nostradamus to these people.
而且Faraday知道一些有趣的规矩
besides,Faraday's got some interesting theories
告诉我们哪些能做  哪些不能做
on what we can and can't do here.
你是说Faraday吗 他在那吗
did you say faraday? he's here?
不在了
not anymore.
带上这个  注意听
put these on and listen up.
Juliet已经处理好了,你们的名字都在名单上
juliet's got it worked out so your name's gonna be on the list,all right?
进去的时候 只要观看那个欢迎录像带
so when you get in there, just watch the little meet and greet video,
当他们叫你的名字时  笑着走上前
wait for 'em to call your name. when they do,just smile,
领取制服和工作任务
step up,take your jumpsuits and work assignments.
工作任务
work assignments?
是的  别担心  接下来的由我来处理
yeah,don't worry. i got it covered.
假装药劲还没过去的样子 因为你才从潜艇上来
just remembe to act a little doped up, 'cause you just woke up from the sub.
如果他们问及一些我们无法回答的问题怎么办
What if they start asking us questions we can't answer,
-就像  1977年的总统  -这不是游戏  Hugo
-like,uh, who's president in 1977? -it's not a damn game show,hugo.
还有  我会一直在这支援你们
besides,i'm gonna be in there to get your backs,all right?
出发
let's move.
Lafleur
Lafleur!
你去哪了 我一直在找你
where have you been? i've been trying to reach you on the walkie.
他们在这干什么
what...what the hell are they doing here?
他们是我们的新兵  一会再解释
they're our new inductees. i'll explain everything later.
别盯着看了 你找我有什么事
stop staring and tell me what your damn problem is.
是  是关于Jin
it's,uh... it's jin.
有个敌方的人在火焰站里
there's a fourteen-j at the flame.
什么
what?
Jin  收到吗
Jin,you there?
James  我们有麻烦了  我们发现了敌人
james,we have a problem. we found a hostile.
什么  什么敌人  在哪
what?! what do you mean you found a hostile? where?
他在林子里游荡
he was wandering in the jungle.
Radzinksy看着他呢
radzinksy's taking care of him now.
他来我们领地干什么
what's he doing in our territory?
这是破坏休战协定的行为
It's a violation of the truce.
是Sayid
it's sayid.
什么
what?!
混蛋
son of a bitch!
还有谁跟他在一起吗
was anyone else with him?
没有  就他自己
no. he was alone.
等等
wait!
对不起  Sun 但是现在我对等你不那么感兴趣
i'm sorry,sun, but waiting doesn't interest me much right now.
这有三个木筏  我要去拿一个
there are three outriggers near here. i'm gonna take one.
你可以来帮我  或者
so you can come along and help me row...
在这等着
or you can stay here.
坦白说  这对我来说没什么不同
Frankly,it make no difference to me.
为什么你要走  为什么要留在那
why are you leaving? why are you staying?
Jin是在 那个主岛上吗
the main island... is that where jin is?
老实说我不知道
honestly,i don't know.
不过如果是我  我会从地方找起
but that's where i'd start looking.
Sun
sun!
在这
over here!
你好  Frank
hello,frank.
你还好吗
you all right?
是的  我没事
yes,i'm fine.
你失踪后  我很担心你
i got worried when i couldn't find ya.
我看到他离开  你们在这里干什么
i saw him leaving. what are you doing out here?
Ben知道哪有船
ben knows where there's a boat.
我要跟他回主岛上去
i'm going back to the main island with him.
难道你真的相信这个家伙
you don't think you can really trust this guy,do ya?
我不得不相信他
i have to trust him.
准备好了吗
you ready?
是的
yes.
Sun
sun.
你考虑一下好吗  这个家伙很危险
i want you to think about this, okay? this guy is dangerous.
Sun  之前我乘坐的那条船
sun, that boat i came here on...
上面都是一群
it was filled with commandos
以他为目标的突击队员
whose only mission was to get him.
结果那些人的下场如何呢
And how'd that work out for everyone?
别去
don't do it.
为什么不跟我们一起走
why don't you come with us?
不行  有很多人要我照顾
i can't. i got a group of people i gotta look after.
没错  Frank
that's right,frank.
船长的首要职责就是他的乘客
a captain's first responsibility is to his passengers.
不过我也有我要照顾的人
but i have people i have to take care of,too.
向南半英里那有一个小码头
there's a small dock about a half mile due south across the water.
那里就是我原来住的村落
it leads directly to a town where i used to live.
那有食物
there are resources there.
如果有人能帮你搞定飞机
so if anyone can help you and the rest of the plane
安全的离开这
get out of here safely,it...
我以为你相信他
i thought you trusted this guy.
我说谎了
i lied.
欢迎来岛上
Welcome to the island.
为了你的安全
For your own comfort and safty,
请不要离开此住宅区
We aske you to remain within your new living quarters.
本区域被高强度的磁场围墙所保护
Our barracks are surrounded by high frequency sonic fence.
我们接下来要怎么做
how are we gonna do this?
Shephard
Shephard?
Jack Shephard
Jack Shephard?
该我了
here we go.
你好 Jack
hey,jack.
请坐
have a seat.
这里也没有
of course it isn't here.
-什么  -你的档案
-what's that? -your file.
那边工作人员够不负责的
could they be any more disorganized on the other side?
对不起
sorry.
我叫Pierre Chang
Namaste. i'm pierre chang.
欢迎加入达摩组织
welcome to the dharma initiative.
旅途顺利吗
How was your ride in?
还好
it was fine.
好  谁是你的驾驶员
good. who was your shuttle driver?
什么
i'm sorry?
接你班车的驾驶员  是哪位
uh... the shuttle from the sub. who was your driver?
是
oh,that was,uh... um...
Lafleur先生
mr. lafleur.
知道了  Lafleur人不错  工作很严谨
ah,yes. good man,lafleur. runs a very tight operation.
对不起  太乱了
i'm sorry for the disorganization.
负责接待你的女士
the woman who was supposed to be processing you in
昨晚刚生了小孩
had a baby last night.
结果我被人从实验室拉出来
i got pulled out of my lab. i...
在这呢
ah,here it is...
你的工作任务
your job assignment.
你被分配到库房
you've been assigned to the shed.
工人  那是什么  那是什么意思
"work man." what does... what does that mean?
按你的能力分配
based on your aptitude test
你负责清洁工作
you'll be doing janitorial work.
你好  小姐
hey there,ma'am. hi.
-他们没叫到你  -没呢  还没
－they haven't called you yet? －no. not yet.
你叫什么名字
what's your name?
Kate
kate...
Austen
Austen.
Austen...
名单上没有你的名字
you're not on my list,
你也不是潜水艇上的乘员
and you're not on the sub manifest either.
谁招的你
who's your recruiter?
恩
um...
等等  Phil
hold on,phil.
我从Amy那拿到新单子了
i just got the new list from amy.
一些是最后才加进来的
some,uh,last-minute additions,
包括  Austen小姐
including... miss austen?
好了
all righty then.
她交给你了
she's all yours.
不好意思搞混了名单
i'm sorry for the mix-up.
我叫  Juliet
i'm juliet.
Kate
kate.
你好Kate
hi,kate.
欢迎来到岛上
welcome to the island.
发生什么了
what the hell happened?
Sayid一个人带着手铐走出林子了
sayid just came walking out of the jungle in handcuffs alone.
什么  他有没有提起他们坐的飞机
what? did he say anything about the plane they were on?
没有  我不能跟他说话  Radzinsky认为他是敌人
no,i couldn't talk to him. radzinsky thinks he's a hostile.
-他不能丢下我们独处  -交给我了
-he won't leave us alone. -i got this.
-他在哪  -关在仓库里了
-where is he? -locked in the storage room.
把钥匙给我
give me the key.
Lafleur  他看到了天鹅站的模型
you need to know,lafleur... he saw the model of the swan,
他可能也看到建立地点的勘测图
and he could've seen the survey of where we're building it.
你的意思是  他是个间谍
your point is? he's a spy.
一切都是在演戏
this whole thing is an act,
要么跟着他演  要么干掉他
and we either play into it or we don't.
我们现在可以结束这一切
we can end this right now.
你在说什么  Radzinsky
what the hell are you talking about,radzinsky?
我们杀了他
we shoot him.
好吧  你的想法非常好
well,i appreciate your input there,quick draw.
可我想先和他谈谈  把该死的钥匙给我
but i wanna talk to him first. give me the damn keys.
我叫  Lafleur  我是安全主管
my name's lafleur. i'm head of security.
我要你仔细听好我说的
i want you to listen real carefully to what i got to say.
照做的话  你就不会有事
and if you do that, you'll be fine.
明白吗
understand?
好吧  我就不废话了
all right, let's start simple.
你要自视为我方的敌人
identify yourself as a hostile.
按照休战协定里所提到的
the terms of the truce say
你必须承认你敌人的身份
you gotta identify yourself as a hostile,
否则我们就有权杀掉你
or we got the right to shoot you.
我们不认为我们是敌人
We do not refer ourselves as hostile
不过很对  我和他们是一伙的
but yes,i-i am one of them.
很好
all right. good.
接下来我们大可友好相待
now we can proceed like a couple of gtlemen.
好吧  我们走
all right,let's go.
带他去兵营
just taking him back to the barracks.
如果你带他走  我必须跟着
oh,if you're taking him in, then i'm coming with you.
这是大错特错
this is a horrible mistake.
-我要直接和Horace报告  -随你便
-i'm gonna talk directly to horace about this. -fine. talk away.
你能说说我们这是在干什么吗
you wanna remind me why the hell we're doing this?
Ben  说如果我老公在岛上
ben said if my husband is on the isle,
那就最好从这里开始找
the best place to start looking for him is here.
我明白了  在你重打他头之前
i see, that's some advice you took
他还给了你一些建议
before you whacked him in the head.
你看到了没
Tell me you saw that
可能只是什么动物
probably just an animal.
动物  好吧
animal. right.
Sun  我很抱歉这样讲
i'm sorry to say,sun, but.
我觉得我们在这里找不到你丈夫
i don't think we're gonna find your husband here.
或许我们应该直接回去
maybe we oughta just head back.
你好
hello.
你是谁
who the hell are you?
我叫 Christian
my name's christian.
我在找我丈夫  他名字叫  Jin Gwon
i'm looking for my husband. his name is jin Gwon.
你知道他在哪里吗
do you know where he is?
跟我走
follow me.
这是哪里
what is this place?
76  78
76,78...
我丈夫在哪里
where is my husband?
找到了  77
here we go. 77.
他在
he's,uh...
他和你的朋友在一起
he's with your friends.
你在说什么  什么朋友
what are you talking about? what friends?
很遗憾  你得花些精力才能找到他
i'm sorry,but you have a bit of a journey ahead of you.
好 准备
okay,ready?
大家一起说  吉祥
everybody say,"namaste!"
吉祥
namaste.
什么玩意儿
nama-what?
好了
okay.
非常好 你们...可以利用剩下的几天熟悉
right on. so you...guys have the rest of the day to get acquainted with
新住处的安全守则
your security protocol handbooks waitin' in your new digs.
有些讲的比较吓人  但我向你们保证
now some of it may seem a little scary,but i promise you all,
我们非常安全  好吧
we are perfectly safe here, okay?
所以在这里别见外
so make yourselves at home.
-我们什么都有 一应俱全  -能听到吗  Phil
come on. we got hamburgers. we got punch. -you there,phil?
-我们带来了个犯人  -收到  Lafeur
-we're coming in with a fourteen-j. roger that,mr. lafleur.
好的   大家靠后站
okay,if i could get everyone to hold back,please,
我们有点安全上的小问题
we have a minor security situation.
走
move.
我想我们找到  Sayid  了
i guess we found sayid.
你就在老实这里呆着  等我们决定怎么处置你
all right,you can hang out here until we can figure out what to do with you.
我们怎么处置他
what are we gonna do with him?
给他弄点吃的 我们不是野蛮人
bring the man some damn food. we're not savages.
打扰
ah,excuse me.
你能告诉我  James Lafleur  住哪里吗
could you tell me where james lafleur lives?
那是他的房子
uh,that's his house right there.
谢谢
thanks.
我不叫他  James
but i wouldn't call him "james."
他比较反感
he hates it.
Jack
hey,jack.
我今天早些时候见过你
i saw you earlier today
当时你在帮Kate我当时想和你聊聊 可是
when you were helping kate, and i wanted to say something to you then,but...
我们不该彼此相识
we're not supposed to know each other.
是啊
yeah. yeah.
-我在找Sawyer我想我来错房间了  -不 进来
-i was looking for sawyer.i guess i came to the wrong house.-no. come in.
晚上好  医生
evening,doc.
我想你们一定有很多话要说
well,i'm sure you two have a lot to talk about.
放松点
take a load off.
喝点啤酒吗
you want a beer?
不  不用了
no. no,i'm fine.
我能帮你点什么  Jack
what can i do for you, jack?
我不知道该从何讲起
i don't even know where to start. uh...
那就谈谈  Sayid  吧
how about with sayid?
我没的选择
i had no choice.
他在丛林中流窜
he was running around in the jungle,
被人抓了起来
got caught by my people.
他看起来不能自我开脱
and seein' as how he can't tell the truth about how he got here,
-我得临时编造  -编造吗
-i had to improvise. -improvise?
现在  Sayid  很安全  这是最重要的
and for now,sayid is safe, which is all that matters.
那我们该何去何从呢
so where do we go from here?
我正在想
i'm working on it.
真的吗  看上去你只是在看书
really? because it looked to me like you were reading a book.
我听说丘吉尔每晚会读一本书
i heard once winston churchill read a book every night,
即使在闪电战时期
even during the blitz.
他说这样有助于思考
he said it made him think better.
我也想像他那样
it's how i like to run things.
我思考
i think.
我相信这对你来说并不重要
I'm sure that doesn't mean that much to you,
以前你做事的时候
'cause back when you were calling the shots,
总是爱冲动
You pretty much just reacted.
知道吗  你不会思考  Jack
See,you didn't think, jack,
据我所知  很多人都死了
And as i recall, a lot of people ended up dead.
我带大家离开了小岛
I got us off the island.
可你现在在这里
But here you are...
回到了原点
Right back where you started.
所以我要继续读书
So i'm gonna go back to reading my book,
我会思考
And i'm gonna think,>
这样我才能在今天救你
'cause that's how i saved your ass today.
这样我以后才能救  Sayid
And that's how i'm gonna save sayid's tomorrow.
你该回家  好好休息下
All you gotta do is go home, get a good night's rest.
让我专心做我的事
Let me do what i do.
难道不是一种解脱吗
Now ain't that a relief?
是啊
Yeah.
Phil
Hey,phil.
我进去送个三明治
I'm just gonna go in there and deliver him a sandwich.
好的
All right.
我给你带了个三明治
I brought you a sandwich.
我没放芥末
I didn't put mustard on it,
如果你需要  我能给你弄点
But if you'd like some, i could get some
这就挺好  谢谢你
This will be fine. thanyou.
你是敌人吗
Are you a hostile?
你觉得我是吗
Do you think i am?
你叫什么
What's your name?
Sayid
Sayid.
你呢
What's yours?
我是 Ben
I'm ben.
幸会  Ben
It's nice to meet you,ben.